Guide to the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 records, 1910-2009; 5739-001; 26.52 cubic feet 31 boxes
  - Series IV: Office Files, 1940-1991 (Box-folder 4/2; 5/3; 5/8; 7/7; 20/2-20/4; 20/8; 20/18; 20/20; 20/22; 31/1-31/10)
    The series is subdivided by function: Subseries A: Constitutions/By-Laws; Subseries B: IBEW Local 46 Agreements; Subseries C: Permit Traveling Card Members Contractor Dispatch; Subseries D: Wiremen Dispatch Records; Subseries E: General Electric Correspondence and Reports; Subseries F: IBEW Bugs; Subseries G: Proclamations; Subseries H: IBEW Authorization for Representation card (blank). Files are arranged chronologically within each subseries.
    - Subseries A: Constitutions/By-Laws, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 7/7; 20/3-20/4)
      - By-Laws, Undated (Box-folder 7/7)
      - King County Labor Council Constitution & By-Laws, 1982 (Box-folder 20/3)
      - Seattle Building & Construction Trades Council Constitution & By-Laws, 1984 (Box-folder 20/4)
    - Subseries B: IBEW Local 46 Agreements, 1978; 1991 (Box-folder 20/2)
    - Subseries C: Permit Traveling Card Members Contractor Dispatch, 1940-1942 (Box-folder 4/2-4/3)
      - Permit Traveling Card Members Contractor Dispatch, 1940 (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Permit Traveling Card Members Contractor Dispatch, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Subseries D: Wiremen Dispatch Records, 1961-1977 (Box-folder 31/1-31/10)
      - Wiremen Dispatch Book, April 1961-January 1962 (Box-folder 31/1)
      - Wiremen Dispatch Book, January 1962-July 1962 (Box-folder 31/2)
      - Wiremen Dispatch Book, July 1962-August 1963 (Box-folder 31/3)
      - Wiremen Dispatch Book, August 1963-December 1965 (Box-folder 31/4)
      - Wiremen Dispatch Book, December 1965-April 1967 (Box-folder 31/5)
      - Wiremen Dispatch Book, April 1967-December 1967 (Box-folder 31/6)
      - Wiremen Dispatch Book, January 1968-September 1968 (Box-folder 31/7)
      - Wiremen Dispatch Book, September 1968-June 1970 (Box-folder 31/8)
      - Wiremen Dispatch Book, June 1970-September 1974 (Box-folder 31/9)
      - Wiremen Dispatch Book, October 1974-November 1977 (Box-folder 31/10)
    - Subseries E: General Electric Correspondence and Reports, 1957 (Box-folder 20/8)
    - Subseries F: IBEW Bugs, Undated (Box-folder 20/18)
    - Subseries G: Proclamations, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 5/8; 20/20)
      - Proclamation for International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 46 Day, October 14, 1989 (Box-folder 20/20)
      - Proclamation for International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Week, 1991 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Subseries H: IBEW Authorization for Representation card (blank), Undated (Box-folder 20/22)
  - Series V: Financial Records, 1940-1947 (Box-folder 4/4-4/5; 5/1)
    Series V includes a small amount of accounting records from the 1940s.
    The series is arranged by function: Subseries A: Accounts Payable; Subseries B: Audits. Subseries B: Audits is further arranged chronologically.
    - Subseries A: Accounts Payable, September 1940-February 1944 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Subseries B: Audits, 1940-1947 (Box-folder 4/4-4/5)
      - Audits, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Audits, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 4/5)
  - Series VI: Education/Training, 1926-1984 (Box-folder 7/9; 13/12; 20/1; 20/6-20/7)
    Series V documents the various exam results for members of Local 46 from the 1920s-1980s. Also included are some items pertaining to the Seattle Marine Electrical Workers and Seattle Electrical Workers Apprenticeship Program.
    The series is arranged by function: Subseries A: Exam Results; Subseries B: New Applicants Journeyman Wireman Test Credits; Subseries C: Seattle Electrical Workers Apprenticeship Standards; Subseries D: Seattle Marine Electrical Workers and Seattle Electrical Workers Apprenticeship Completion Banquet.
    - Subseries A: Exam Results, 1926-1949 (Box-folder 7/9)
    - Subseries B: New Applicants Journeyman Wireman Test Credits, January 1969-March 1982 (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Subseries C: Seattle Electrical Workers Apprenticeship Standards, 1969 (Box-folder 20/1)
    - Subseries D: Seattle Marine Electrical Workers and Seattle Electrical Workers Apprenticeship Completion Banquet, 1984 (Box-folder 20/6-20/7)
      - Seattle Marine Electrical Workers and Seattle Electrical Workers Apprenticeship Completion Banquet Program, 1984 (Box-folder 20/6)
      - Seattle Marine Electrical Workers and Seattle Electrical Workers Apprenticeship Completion Banquet Guest Book, undated (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Series VII: Publications & Reports, 1945-1996 (Box-folder 5/9; 20/5; 20/9-20/17; 20/19; 20/21)
    Series VII includes various magazines, newspapers, reports and directories of interest to Local 46. The bulk of the items date from the 1950s-1960s.
    The series is arranged by originating body: Subseries A: Local 46 Newspaper Advertisements; Subseries B: Marine Digest; Subseries C: Busy B-11 IBEW National Magazine, Vol. 2 - No. 2; Subseries D: United States Department of Labor Employment and Earnings Reports; Subseries E: Directories; Subseries F: Seattle Union Record Newspaper. Within each subseries items are arranged chronologically.
    - Subseries A: Local 46 Newspaper Advertisements, 1961 (Box-folder 20/19)
    - Subseries B: Marine Digest, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 20/12-20/17)
      - Marine Digest, Volume 38: Number 18, 1960 (Box-folder 20/12)
      - Marine Digest, Volume 39: Numbers 40-45, 1961 (Box-folder 20/13)
      - Marine Digest, Volume 39: Numbers 46-52, 1961 (Box-folder 20/14)
      - Marine Digest, Volume 40: Numbers 1-7, 1962 (Box-folder 20/15)
      - Marine Digest, Volume 40: Numbers 8-14, 1962 (Box-folder 20/16)
      - Marine Digest, Volume 40: Numbers 15-17, 1962 (Box-folder 20/17)
    - Subseries C: Busy B-11 IBEW National Magazine, Vol. 2 - No. 2, January 1945 (Box-folder 20/21)
    - Subseries D: United States Department of Labor Employment and Earnings Reports, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 20/10-20/11)
      - United States Department of Labor Employment and Earnings Report, 1956 (Box-folder 20/10)
      - United States Department of Labor Employment and Earnings Report, 1957 (Box-folder 20/11)
    - Subseries E: Directories, 1961-1996 (Box-folder 20/5; 20/9)
      - Marine Digest Pacific Northwest Maritime Directory, 1961 (Box-folder 20/9)
      - Washington State Labor Council AFL-CIO Directory of Organizations, 1996 (Box-folder 20/5)
    - Subseries F: Seattle Union Record Newspaper, 1991 (Box-folder 5/9)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 records, 1902-2014; 5739-002; 20.65 cubic feet 20 boxes and 2 oversized folders
  The accession is arranged into 8 series.
  Series I: Meeting Minutes and Registers
  Series II: Dispatch Books and Registers
  Series VI: Conferences and Conventions
  Series VII: Publications and Reports
  Meeting Minutes and Registers (Series I), Dispatch Books and Registers (Series II), Conferences and Conventions (Series VI), and Publications and Reports (Series VII) are arranged into subseries according to originating body. Contract Negotiations (Series III), Office Files (Series IV), and Photographs and Historical Materials (Series VIII) are arranged into subseries by function. Financial Records (Series V), is not divided into subseries. Contract Negotiations (Series III), is arranged alphabetically within each subseries. All other subseries, and Financial Records (Series V), are arranged chronologically according to the oldest document in each file.
  A large part of the collection is the Meeting Minutes & Registers (Series I), which document the issues most pertinent to the Union and its members. Another large portion of the collection is Publications and Reports (Series VII), which contains publications collected by officers of Local 46 as well as a long history of newsletters, papers and reports published by the union. Another large portion of the collection is Contract Negotiations (Series III), which showcases the evolvement of contracts, and workers rights as a whole, over time. Of particular note in this collection is the detailed history of the union, put together by Bob Gorman and Local 46’s History Committee, in Photographs and Historical Materials (Series VIII). The day-to-day workings of the IBEW can be assessed from Dispatch Books and Registers (Series II), Office Files (Series IV), and Financial Records (Series V). In addition, Conferences and Conventions (Series VI), offers information, commemorative publications and photographs about various union gatherings such as anniversary celebrations, banquets, official conferences, and large conventions throughout the union’s history.
  Open to all users
  - Series I: Meeting Minutes and Registers, 1937-2002 (Box-folder 1/1-4/5; 16/1; 4/6-4/10)
    The series is subdivided by originating body: Subseries A: Bremerton Unit #9; Subseries B: Broadcast Unit; Subseries C: Building Managers; Subseries D: Electronic Unit; Subseries E: Executive Board; Subseries F: General Meetings; Subseries G: Joint Apprenticeship Training Committee; Subseries H: Manufacturing Unit; Subseries I: Marine Unit; Subseries J: Motor Shop; Subseries K: Neon Sign Unit; Subseries L: Oil Burner Unit; Subseries M: Refrigeration; Subseries N: Residential Unit; Subseries O: Safety Committee; Subseries P: Wireman’s Unit; Subseries Q: Port Angeles Unit 8. Subseries are arranged chronologically.
    Series I includes Meeting Minutes for the general membership and specific units of Local 46 from 1937-2002, as well as a handful of unit-specific registers on exam attendance and jobs worked.
    - Subseries A: Bremerton Unit #9, 1975-1987 (Box-folder 1/1-1/2)
      - Bremerton Unit #9 Meeting Minutes, November 1975-August 1981 (Box-folder 1/1)
      - Bremerton Unit #9 Meeting Minutes, September 1981-June 1987 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Subseries B: Broadcast Unit, June 1986-November 1993 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Subseries C: Building Managers, 1977-1990 (Box-folder 1/4-1/6)
      - Building Managers Meeting Minutes, January 1977-November 1979 (Box-folder 1/4)
      - Building Managers Meeting Minutes, November 1979-March 1984 (Box-folder 1/5)
      - Building Managers Meeting Minutes, March 1984-April 1990 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Subseries D: Electronic Unit, 1976-1989 (Box-folder 1/7-1/8)
      - Electronic Unit Meeting Minutes, July 1976-March 1982 (Box-folder 1/7)
      - Electronic Unit Meeting Minutes, April 1982-December 1989 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Subseries E: Executive Board, 1975-1988 (Box-folder 1/9-2/5)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, May 1975-April 1977 (Box-folder 1/9)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, May 1977-February 1979 (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, February 1979-August 1980 (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, August 1980-November 1981 (Box-folder 2/3)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, December 1981-October 1984 (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, October 1984-March 1988 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Subseries F: General Meetings, 1976-1987 (Box-folder 2/6-3/1)
      - General Meeting Minutes, March 1976-October 1981 (Box-folder 2/6)
      - General Meeting Minutes, November 1981-March 1987 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - Subseries G: Joint Apprenticeship Training Committee, April 1967-July 1978 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Subseries H: Manufacturing Unit, March 1957-July 1958 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Subseries I: Marine Unit, 1973-1987 (Box-folder 3/4-3/5)
      - Marine Unit Meeting Minutes, March 1973-August 1981 (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Marine Unit Meeting Minutes, September 1981-June 1987 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - Subseries J: Motor Shop, 1971-1989 (Box-folder 3/6-3/7)
      - Motor Shop Meeting Minutes, November 1971-November 1986 (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Motor Shop Meeting Minutes, December 1986-November 1989 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - Subseries K: Neon Sign Unit, 1982-1992 (Box-folder 4/1-4/2)
      - Neon Sign Unit Register and Meeting Minutes, January 1982-June 1992 (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Neon Sign Unit Meeting Minutes, December 1982-March 1988 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Subseries L: Oil Burner Unit, October 1975-August 1985 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Subseries M: Refrigeration, January 1937-December 1938 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Subseries N: Residential Unit, June 1976-May 1982 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Subseries O: Safety Committee, March 1985-June 2002 (Box-folder 16/1)
    - Subseries P: Wireman's Unit, 1971-2001 (Box-folder 4/6-4/8)
      - Wireman's Unit Meeting Minutes, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Appeared to Seek Permission to Sit Journeyman Wireman Exam Register, 1974-1988 (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Appeared to Seek Permission to Sit Journeyman Wireman Exam Register, 1988-2001 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Subseries Q: Port Angeles Unit 8, 1957-1990 (Box-folder 4/9-4/10)
      - Port Angeles Unit 8 Meeting Minutes, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 4/9)
      - Port Angeles Unit 8 Meeting Minutes, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 4/10)
  - Series II: Dispatch Books and Registers, 1940-2008 (Box-folder 5/1-5/10; 16/2-17/2; 5/11-6/9)
    The series is subdivided by originating body: Subseries A: Bremerton Unit #9; Subseries B: Electricians Unit; Subseries C: General; Subseries D: Marine Unit; Subseries E: Motor Shop EFE Dispatch Log; Subseries F: Permit Men Log; Subseries G: Port Angeles Unit; Subseries H: Sound and Communications; Subseries I: Stockman Out of Work List; Subseries J: Wireman. All subseries are further arranged chronologically.
    Series II includes Dispatch Books and Registers for the general membership of Local 46 from 1940-2008, as well as a handful of employer request registers, dispatch logs, and out-of-work registers for the union.
    - Subseries A: Bremerton Unit #9, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 5/1-5/2)
      - IBEW Local #46-9 Dispatch Ledger, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 5/1)
      - IBEW Local #46-9 Dispatch Ledger, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Subseries B: Electricians Unit, 1983-2008 (Box-folder 5/3-5/4)
      - Electricians Local 46 Register, 1983-2003 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Electricians Local 46 Register, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Subseries C: General, 1941-1993 (Box-folder 5/5-5/10; 16/2-17/2; 5/11-5/12)
      - Dispatch Log, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Dispatch Log, 1951-1953 (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Out of Work Register, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Out of Work Register, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Out of Work Register, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Oil Burning / Radio-TV-Sound / Appliance Repair Dispatch Log, 1963-1997 (Box-folder 5/10)
      - Employer Request Register, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 16/2)
      - Employer Request Register, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 17/1)
      - Employer Request Register, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 17/2)
      - Dispatch Log, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Dispatch Log, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - Subseries D: Marine Unit, 1956-1981 (Box-folder 5/13-5/14)
      - Marine Unit Out of Work Register, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Marine Unit E.F.E. Dispatch Log, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 5/14)
    - Subseries E: Motor Shop EFE Dispatch Log, 1963-1977 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - Subseries F: Permit Men Log, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Subseries G: Port Angeles Unit, 1955-1988 (Box-folder 5/17-6/1)
      - Port Angeles Unit Meeting Register, 1955-1975 (Box-folder 5/17)
      - Port Angeles Unit Dispatch Log, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Subseries H: Sound & Communications, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 6/2-6/4)
      - Sound and Communication Day Book Referrals, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - Teledata - Sound & Communications - TV Repair - Appliance Repair Dispatch Log, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 6/3)
      - Sound and Communication Sign In Book, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - Subseries I: Stockman Out of Work List, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Subseries J: Wiremen, 1956-1979 (Box-folder 6/6-6/9)
      - Wiremen's Unit Out of Work Register, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 6/6)
      - Wiremen's Unit Out of Work Register, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 6/7)
      - Wiremen's Unit Out of Work Register, 1959 (Box-folder 6/8)
      - House Wiremen's Dispatch Book, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 6/9)
  - Series III: Contract Negotiations, 1934-1999 (Box-folder 7/1-9/24)
    The series is subdivided by function: Subseries A: Negotiations Files; Subseries B: Minutes, Pacific Coast Shipbuilding Negotiating Conference; Subseries C: Labor Agreements; Subseries D: Agreement Briefs; Subseries E: Negotiating Committee Member Notes. Subseries are further arranged chronologically.
    Series III includes detailed records of contract negotiations and resulting labor agreements from 1934-1999, as well as a handful of legal briefs and instances of contract enforcement by the union.
    - Subseries A: Negotiations Files, 1958-1999 (Box-folder 7/1-8/25)
      - Aldi Electronics Contract Negotiations, 1973 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Bellevue Public Schools Contract Negotiations, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 7/2)
      - Bellevue Public Schools Contract Negotiations, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 7/3)
      - City of Seattle and the Joint Crafts Council: Negotiations, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 7/4)
      - City of Seattle Negotiations, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 7/5)
      - City of Seattle Negotiations, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 7/6)
      - Consolidated Electric Corporation Contract Negotiations, 1970-1980 (Box-folder 7/7)
      - Consolidated Electric Contract Negotiations, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 7/8)
      - Duwamish Shipyard, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 7/9)
      - Electric Motor and Equipment Shop Contractors Contract Negotiations, 1960-1980 (Box-folder 7/10)
      - Electric Motor and Equipment Shop Contractors Contract Negotiations, 1965-1981 (Box-folder 7/11)
      - Electric Motor and Equipment Shop Contractors Contract Negotiations, 1972-1981 (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Electronic Services, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 7/13)
      - Fishing Vessel Owners Marine Ways Contract Negotiations, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 7/14)
      - Foss Maritime Company Contract Negotiations, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 7/15)
      - Harris Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1974-1989 (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Hendricks Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1974 (Box-folder 7/17)
      - International Marine Systems, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 7/18)
      - Joint Crafts Council Meeting Minutes, Correspondence, and Notes, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 7/19)
      - Minutes, 1974 Joint Ship Building and Ship Repair Negotiations (Box-folder 7/20)
      - Minutes, 1980 Joint Ship Building and Ship Repair Negotiations (Box-folder 7/21)
      - Minutes, 1983 Joint Ship Building and Ship Repair Negotiations (Box-folder 7/22)
      - Lunde Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1974-1986 (Box-folder 7/23)
      - Marine Controls Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1974 (Box-folder 7/24)
      - Marine Industries Northwest, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1982 (Box-folder 7/25)
      - Marine Power and Equipment Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 7/26)
      - Negotiations, 1958 (Box-folder 7/27)
      - Negotiations, 1959 (Box-folder 7/28)
      - Nemco Electric Contract Negotiations, 1960-1976 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Nemco Electric Contract Negotiations, 1960-1976 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Nemco Electric Contract Negotiations, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Nemco Electric Contract Negotiations, 1979 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Northwestern Glass Company Contract Negotiations, 1971-1980 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Northwestern Glass Company Contract Negotiations, 1964-1980 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Pacific Coast Master Agreement Contract Negotiations, 1965-1977 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Puget Sound Chapter of the National Electrical Contractors Association Contract Negotiations: Information for Oral Testimony, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Seattle Times Contract Negotiations, 1989-1999 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Snelson Anvil Contract Negotiations, 1988 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Todd Pacific Shipyards Corporation Contract Negotiations, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Todd Pacific Shipyards Contract Negotiation, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Walashek Industries Contract Negotiations, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Washington Employers, Inc. on behalf of the EPCON Company, Heath Sign Company, National Sign Company, and Tube-Art Displays, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1968 (Box-folder 8/14)
      - Washington Metal Trades Contract Negotiations, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Washington State Boat Builders and Associates Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1969-1989 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Washington State Boat Builders and Associates, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Washington State Department of Transportation, Marine Division Contract Negotiations, 1985 (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Washington State Ferries (Maintenance) Contract Negotiations, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Washington State Ferries Contract Negotiations, 1969-1989 (Box-folder 8/20)
      - Washington State Ferries Contract Negotiations, 1976-1989 (Box-folder 8/21)
      - Washington State Highway Commission Contract Negotiations, 1967 (Box-folder 8/22)
      - West Fuel Company Contract Negotiations, 1974 (Box-folder 8/23)
      - Wireman's Negotiations, 1958 (Box-folder 8/24)
      - Wright Schuchart Harbor Co. Contract Negotiations, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 8/25)
    - Subseries B: Minutes, Pacific Coast Shipbuilding Negotiating Conference, 1962 (Box-folder 8/26)
    - Subseries C: Labor Agreements, 1934-1993 (Box-folder 8/27-9/9)
      - Agreements with other Local and Regional Organizations 1 of 4, 1965-1993 (Box-folder 8/27)
      - Agreements with other Local and Regional Organizations 2 of 4, 1965-1993 (Box-folder 8/28)
      - Agreements with other Local and Regional Organizations 3 of 4, 1965-1993 (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Agreements with other Local and Regional Organizations 4 of 4, 1965-1993 (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Electric Contractor Association Labor Agreement, 1934 (Box-folder 9/3)
      - Labor Agreements, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Longshore and Harbor Workers' Compensation Act Amendments of 1984 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - Inside Wiremans Agreement between IBEW No. 46 and National Electrical Contractors Association Puget Sound Chapter, 1965 (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Contract: Local 46 and Puget Sound Chapter, National Electrical Contractors Association, 1994 (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Shoreline Public Schools Agreement, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Wireman Agreement, 1934 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Subseries D: Agreement Briefs, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 9/10-9/13)
      - Puget Sound Chapter of the National Electrical Contractors Association Contract Negotiations: Hightime Briefs, 1977 (Box-folder 9/10)
      - Puget Sound Chapter of the National Electrical Contractors Association Contract Negotiations: Residential Agreement Briefs, 1977 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Puget Sound Chapter of the National Electrical Contractors Association Contract Negotiations: Residential Agreement Briefs, 1979 (Box-folder 9/12)
      - Puget Sound Chapter of the National Electrical Contractors Association Contract Negotiations: Residential Agreement Briefs, 1984 (Box-folder 9/13)
    - Subseries E: Negotiating Committee Member Notes, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 9/14-9/24)
      - Negotiating Committee: Alfred F. Gruenwald, 1962 (Box-folder 9/14)
      - Negotiating Committee: Alfred F. Gruenwald, 1963 (Box-folder 9/15)
      - Negotiating Committee: Duane Mooney, 1963 (Box-folder 9/16)
      - Negotiating Committee: Don Dorr, 1963 (Box-folder 9/17)
      - Negotiating Committee: Edward B. Olson, 1962 (Box-folder 9/18)
      - Negotiating Committee: Gene Nelson, 1960 (Box-folder 9/19)